http://www.ecmi.org/en/privacy-statement2

Menu
Search:
Search
Privacy StatementStatement of Faith
Privacy StatementECM is committed to protecting your privacy online. This statement explains how we will do this. We will review this statement in the light of comments we receive so please check the latest version.If you have any questions about how we handle your personal data, please do get in touch with the appropriate ECM office.
Personal InformationIf you provide personal data it will be processed fairly.
"Personal Data" is any data about you, even if it is in the public domain, eg. name, address, phone number.
"Processed" includes gathering, exchanging and storing data.
"Fairly" requires consent ( which may be implied) from you based on your knowledge of the use of that data.
What information do we collect?If you are making an enquiry via a web form, we may store your name and contact details (email address and/or telephone number). We also collect other information automatically, as described below.
Automatically collected informationWe automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us on our sites and in internal e-mail correspondence. Automatic technologies we use may include, for example, Web server logs/IP addresses, cookies and Web beacons.
Web Server Logs/IP Addresses. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. All computer identification on the Internet is conducted with IP addresses, which allows computers and servers to recognise and communicate with each other. ECM International collects IP addresses via Google Analytics in order to conduct site analysis and Web site performance review.
Cookies. A cookie is a piece of information that is placed automatically on your computer’s hard drive when you access certain Web sites. The cookie uniquely identifies your browser to the server. Cookies allow us to store information on the server to help make the Web experience better for you and to conduct site analysis and Web site performance review. Most Web browsers are set up to accept cookies, although you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Note, however, that some portions of our sites may not work properly if you refuse cookies.
Web Beacons. On certain Web pages or e-mails, ECM International may utilize a common Internet technology called a “Web beacon” (also known as an “action tag” or “clear GIF technology.”) Web beacons help analyse the effectiveness of Web sites by measuring, for example, the number of visitors to a site or how many visitors clicked on key elements of a site.
Web beacons, cookies and other tracking technologies do not automatically obtain personally identifiable information about you. Only if you voluntarily submit personally identifiable information, such as by registering or sending e-mails, can these automatic tracking technologies be used to provide further information about your use of the Web sites and/or interactive e-mails to improve their usefulness to you.
How do we use your information?We use the details you submit to send you information you have requested.By providing data through this site you are giving consent for it to be processed fairly.
When do we share information?We do not give or sell your personal information to other organisations.We will keep your information secure and not use it for other purposes without consent.Other web sites may have links on our site. If you follow the link to these sites, they may collect information, and such sites are not within our control.This ECM privacy statement covers this website and ECM Ministries.If we believe that your use of the site is unlawful, we reserve the right to disclose any information we have obtained through the site about you to the extent that it is reasonably necessary in our opinion to prevent, remedy or take action in relation to such conduct.
Legal NoticeYour use of this web site hosted by European Christian Mission International (referred to as "ECM") is subject to the following terms and conditions:
Copyright and Trade MarksAll materials on this web site are the copyright of ECM or are reproduced with permission from other copyright owners. All rights are reserved. The materials on this web site may be retrieved and downloaded solely for personal use. No materials may otherwise be copied, modified, published, broadcast or otherwise distributed without the prior written permission of ECM.
DisclaimerECM makes no warranties or representations of any kind concerning the accuracy or suitability of the information contained on this web site for any purpose. ECM makes no warranties or representations of any kind that the services provided by this web site will be uninterrupted, error-free or that the web site or the server that hosts the web site are free from viruses or other forms of harmful computer code. In no event shall ECM, its workers or agents be liable for any direct, indirect or consequential damages resulting from the use of this web site.This exclusion and limitation only applies to the extent permitted by law and is without prejudice to any express provisions to the contrary in any written license or agreement from ECM in respect of the use of any online service provided via this web site.
LinksLinks to other web sites are provided by ECM in good faith and for information only. ECM disclaims any responsibility for the materials contained in any web site linked to this site.
Interactive materialPortions of this site may allow users to post their own material. Materials posted by users do not necessarily reflect the views of ECM.By posting materials on this site, you represent that you have all necessary rights in and to such materials and that such materials will not infringe on the personal or proprietary rights of any third parties, nor will such materials be defamatory, unlawful, threatening, obscene or otherwise objectionable.ECM reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to review, edit or delete any material posted by users which ECM deems defamatory, unlawful, threatening, obscene or otherwise objectionable. Notwithstanding the foregoing, ECM expressly disclaims any responsibility or liability for any material communicated by third parties through this web site.
The SystemUnauthorised access to this web system is forbidden. Your use of this web site is subject to your agreement not to in any way compromise it or the system it is built on.
You can review your cookie settings here and change them as necessary. Read more about our usage of cookies in our Privacy statement.
Strictly necessary
You will only receive cookies which are needed for this website to function properly. You cannot disable these cookies.
Preferences
This website stores your preferences so they can be applied during your next visit.
Analysis
This website analyses how it is being used, so that its functionality can be amended and improved. The data collected is anonymous. Help us improve our website!
Tracking
This website analyses your visit, so its content can be tailored to your needs.
External
This website makes use of external functionalities such as social media sharing options.
Save cookie settings
What can I do?Pray for the workersMake a donationSupport ECM by using EveryclickService opportunitiesFAQECM in EuropeECM's WorkersWhere is ECM involved in Europe?ECM's Partner organisationsRevival in the BalkansThe Need in EuropeMore about ECMECM TrailerECM on YoutubeECMI annual reportsStatement of FaithECM ValuesPrivacy statementECM member pagesiGuideiTraining-DevelopmentiMember CareECM WebMailECM Document ServerMember Login
Donate now
Facebook
Twitter
YouTube
Vimeo
Disclaimer
Switch to another country site
Close
HomeEuropeThe Bigger PictureOur ValuesDiscipleship and Planting ChurchesWorking togetherLove in ActionOur HistoryGoLong Term OpportunitiesShort Term OpportunitiesGetting startedVolunteerValues of ECMPrayPrayStories from EuropeGiveContactContactChange of addressSubscribeECM Offices
Donate now
